    <release version="1.24.8220" date="2024-08-22">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.8220</url>
        <description>
- [New] : Now you can see list of space with access on click of Limited Visibility button
- [New Labs] You can now ask Acter to sync the events you haven't declined yet to your system calendar (on certain devices) including a reminder. As of now, this is behind a labs-feature flag you need to activate manually while we are rolling this out.

- Rename process from app to acter in task manager on windows

- [Enhancement] : UI-UX improvement of pin details page
- [Enhancement] : UI-UX improvement of Attachment List
- [New] : You can now add one or more links to attachments 
- [New] : While creating pin, you can give customised name to your selected attachments by setting relevant title data
- Keep the app alive in background and close to the tray icon only (on supported platforms)

- fix bug where chat input cursor jumps to end of text in middle of edit.
- make chat send button more robust to respond to text composing state.

- Fix a bug that the chat list search results wouldn't properly update upon keystrokes

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.8080" date="2024-08-08">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.8080</url>
        <description>

- Fix on showing the relations of spaces and chats properly if you've left any of the rooms

- replace ref.invalidate() with proper notifiers that listen to SDK events

- Fix bug in quick jump navigation, where it used to go black rather than properly jump sometimes

- Fix uploading of my Avatar: no more crashing, instant updating

- [Chats]: various fixes has been done which cause input cursor to lose focus when interacting with emoji picker, swipe-reply/edit and sending messages.
- [Chats]: bug fix where on desktop, input doesn't go multi-line when shift+enter.
- [Chats]: bug fix on mentions when suggestions don't come up with name of user.

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.8010" date="2024-08-01">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.8010</url>
        <description>
- You can now easily "close" chats and spaces as an admin.

- Fix in routing if you resized the app window while in setting screens.

- Acter is now available in french!


- Show the progress when inviting many users via other spaces
- Pull to refresh for Space Overview page

- [New] : Better visualisation of Ongoing, Upcoming and Past events by colours
- [New] : Event listing screen contains Search and Filters option for better explore your events
- [Fix] : Now dashboard will show events which you are attending
- Sending attachment in chats works again
- Removing attachments from Pins and other objects works again

- Fix issue in displaying chats of a space if there aren't any further to show

- Now when you mention some user in chat, the styling colors will appear on name/id.

- We have massively improved the performance of the chats section


        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7250" date="2024-07-25">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7250</url>
        <description>
- [Improvement] : Space Details : Space Header now also show members list UI
- [Enhancement] : Space Details : Click on section Header labels now lead you to relevant detail page
- [Improvement] : Hide unwanted avatar UI on message thread if it is DM
- [Fixes] : Disable invite button in Room Details page if it is DM
- [Improvement] : Couple of UI fixes on chat listing and Filters Area
- [Fixes] : Close attachment selection option dialog upon tab

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7231" date="2024-07-23">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7231</url>
        <description>
- Missing a subspace or subchat? You can now click the refresh button on the sub screens and we will fetch teh latest version from the server.


[bugfix] : Fix bug that force logout doesn't work in session card (issue#1239)

- You can now use the cool share feature right from the super-invites list in your settings

- Admins can now suggest other spaces & chats from a space. These are then shown to a user when they enter the spaces for the first time with a convenient function to quickly join them or subset of them

- Chat mentions are much more optimized and efficient in bringing up users even on large rooms.
- Swipe-to-reply/edit feature is now disabled on deleted/encrypted messages as intended with chat message actions.

- Create a default sub-chat with just the toggle of a button at Space creation

- [Improvement] : Better inline edit features for space topic, description and avatar without going through edit space screen
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7180" date="2024-07-18">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7180</url>
        <description>
- Fix: Avatars some time showed up weird, were broken or didn't show at all
- Fix: Several instances in which the App failed or froze because of broken Avatars


[Improvement] : Now you can view space and group chat avatar in full screen
[Improvement] : If you have permission than you can have inline avatar change option instead of go to any detail screen
[New] : You can zoom in and out avatar view for better visualisation
- Fix to show invite code even after managing it
- Show the number of additional rooms associated with an invite code (if any)
- Allows you to select the invite code if more than one is possible

- Simplify onboarding, drop unnecessary screens
- Automatic Crash analytics if you opt-in to that

- [Improvement] : Task list UI is now more consistent and robust
- [New] : Now you can search any task list by it's title name
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7123" date="2024-07-12">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7123</url>
        <description>
# Changes since v1.24.7120 
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7121" date="2024-07-12">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7121</url>
        <description>
# Changes since v1.24.7120 
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.7120" date="2024-07-12">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.7120</url>
        <description>
# Changes since release-latest 
- Switching to black background and bolder blue colors for highlights for better contrast
- Fix to make sure the description of the visibility items is legible 
- Fixed the chat rooms list ordering based on latest message timestamp.

- [Improvement] Total overhaul of the Space Detail Screen replacing the navigation with a fresh and variable top bar navigation, nice intro sections with full-screen-views of the actual features and quick actions on the bottom (if you have the rights to). Making the space screen a more mobile-friendly and nicer to work with.
- [fixes] General UI and Color issues fixes
- [Improvement] : Pins list UI is now more consistent and robust
- [New] : Now you can search any pin by it's title name
- At PR#1783, many fns for password rest were made and some of them are unnecessary or duplicated. Will refactor them.

- Fix inviting all space members to chat room, fixes #1895
- Do not render link previews for room and user mentions, fixes #1604
- Fix chat input Capitalization, fixes #1902
- Fix support for proper user mentions and room links, fixes #1829

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.6270" date="2024-06-27">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.6270</url>
        <description>
# Changes since release-latest 
- [Improvement] : Optimised application color system
- Tasks and ToDo-List have left the lab and are now on by default for everyone.

- SuperInvites can now be easily managed from the Room Invite screen
- SuperInvite Codes are generated with the room display name as a prefix and additional numbers now

- Task item detail page UI-UX enhancement
- My task list on home screen optimised with compact design and better visual indications 
- Minor fix to dismiss the keyboard after submitting a comment & making the icons on the image overlay accessible regardless of top bezels

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.3624" date="2024-06-24">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3624</url>
        <description>
# Changes since v1.24.3620 
- [Fixes] : Wrong image/video in update slide issue is resolved
- You can now reset your password just with your email address, if you previously confirmed your email address connected to that account.

- Now shows unconfirmed emails on Activities screen to nudge you to confirm them


- [new] You can now report any Task item and Task List
- [new] You can now delete any Task item and Task List
- You can now see multiple parent avatars on space overview if it's linked as sub-space of it.

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.3613" date="2024-06-13">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3613</url>
        <description>
# Changes since v1.24.3530 
- Notifications were not always properly activated upon first registration, this is now fixed. You might be prompted to allow notifications (once) upon a fresh start of the app if you had run into this problem before (without knowing).

- Improved layout of selected emoji reactions in chat: takes up less space, should be easier to grasp on a quick view.

- Reworked the API to create TaskLists and Tasks

- As an admin of a space you are now able to redact any space item as well (e.g. Pin, Event) not only as the author.

- As a space admin you can now link subspace and space chats right from the empty screen

- You can now bookmark spaces, too. If you have bookmarked spaces they will show on your home screen rather than the full list.

- [fix] do not send typing notifications if the user disabled that in the settings
- [fix] only one room could be receiving typing state at a time despite multiple rooms actually being in that state.

- You can now configure the rules to join a space or chat room, including making it public and limiting it to a set of spaces, whose members can join directly.
- Indicator in the Space header shows who can access that space

- Next to sharing an Attachment & iCal you can now download them, if your device supports that.

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.3506" date="2024-05-06">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3506</url>
        <description>
# Changes since v1.24.3502 
- The search of the public directory has been completely rewritten with an improved UI, better interactive items and cleaner overall flow. Several other publicly known servers have been allowing you to easily select and search them without having to know the exact address, and you can search spaces and chat rooms within the same widget now.
- You can now add any room uri in the quick jump as well and directly join from there
- When what you are looking for is not found in the quick jump, searching the public directory for that term is offered right away, making it easier to find existing rooms
- Support for parsing `matrix://`-URI has been added to the public search and quick jump search

- [fix]: Space and Chats invitation now properly shows invite/join state of user relative to room upon searching via public directory/direct invite.

- [new]: You can now update chat profile details (Name, Topic & Avatar) for chats you are admin of
- The app is now available in Polish. It will be autoselected if this is your system language and you didn't pick any language via the settings before. You can change your preferred language in your Profile settings.

        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.3425" date="2024-04-25">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3425</url>
        <description>
# Changes since release-latest 
- [feat.]: More interactivity comes with Attachments, now image and video attachments are enabled to be viewed in full screen while other files can be shared natively.
- [fix]: Attachments selection is also now shown on the desktop, allowing you to choose specific file types for upload.

- [feat.] Chat now shows typing notifications to inform you who's been typing. This setting is enabled by default but can be turned off in App Settings -> Chat Settings.

- Several smaller fixes around the Chat input: it's now properly resetting the edit/reply-to message, marks the right message for editing (your own), shows the editable content and has better icons for the different swipe-actions

- You can now share any Event as an iCalendar item with the outside world.

        </description>
    </release>

    <release version="1.24.3411" date="2024-04-11">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3402</url>
        <description>
        # Changes since 1.24.3405
- [feat.]: More interactivity comes with Attachments, now image and video attachments are enabled to be viewed in full screen while other files can be shared natively.
- [fix]: Attachments selection is also now shown on the desktop, allowing you to choose specific file types for upload.
- Comments & Attachments are available for Tasks, TaskLists and Events
- The comments lab feature is now on by default. You can still turn it if it bothers you
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.24.3405" date="2024-04-05">
        <url type="details">https://github.com/acterglobal/a3/releases/tag/v1.24.3405</url>
        <description>
        # Changes since v1.24.2328 
        - [Enhancement] : UI-UX enhancements on user onboarding flow
        - new labs feature: Pins have comments now (if you activate the labs)

        - You can now delete attachments from pin with the help of minus icon (showing, if having necessary permissions) on attachment item.

        - You can now kick (and ban) any user from a space or chat through the recently introduced member-info-drawer (by clicking on the user avatar almost everywhere).

        - [Enhancement] : Now user can toggle password visibility on login and register account screens
        - [Enhancement] : UI-UX enhancements on user onboarding flow
        </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
<component>